rblbank.com 2016-06-29

# Privacy Policy You agree that we may use Customer Information for the purpose of statistical analysis and for creation of data ("Statistical Information"), which does not contain individual Customer Information. In addition to the information that the Bank elicits from you, you are free to volunteer any other information that you feel that the Bank needs to know, but the security and confidentiality as per this Policy is guaranteed only to the information that the Bank directly asks from you. This Policy holds true for a non-customer who has provided information to the Bank, by any means, with the intentions of establishing a relationship, of whatsoever nature, with the Bank. By divulging any information to us you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy. Use of Customer Information / Statistical Information We may use the Customer Information for, among other things, customer verification, provision of products and services, for personalization of products or services, marketing or promotion of our financial services or related products or that of our associates and affiliates; for creation of Statistical Information, statistical analysis or credit scoring, enforcement of your obligations, any other purpose that will help us in providing you with optimal and high quality services. Security: We have taken reasonable measures to protect security and confidentiality of the Customer Information and its transmission through the World Wide Web. You are required to follow the Terms and Conditions while using this Website including the instructions stated therein in respect of security and confidentiality of your Log-in and Password. The Bank will give access to Customer Information to only authorised employees. Employees who violate this Privacy Policy shall be subject to disciplinary process as per the byelaws of the Bank. Any employee who withdraws from the employment of the Bank will have to undertake to abide by this Privacy Policy and keep all Customer Information secure and confidential. Disclosure

Privacy Policy
You agree that we may use Customer Information for the purpose of statistical analysis and
for creation of data ("Statistical Information"), which does not contain individual Customer
Information. In addition to the information that the Bank elicits from you, you are free to
volunteer any other information that you feel that the Bank needs to know, but the security
and confidentiality as per this Policy is guaranteed only to the information that the Bank
directly asks from you.
This Policy holds true for a non-customer who has provided information to the Bank, by any
means, with the intentions of establishing a relationship, of whatsoever nature, with the Bank.
By divulging any information to us you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy.
Use of Customer Information / Statistical Information We may use the Customer Information
for, among other things, customer verification, provision of products and services, for
personalization of products or services, marketing or promotion of our financial services or
related products or that of our associates and affiliates; for creation of Statistical Information,
statistical analysis or credit scoring, enforcement of your obligations, any other purpose that
will help us in providing you with optimal and high quality services.
Security: We have taken reasonable measures to protect security and confidentiality of the
Customer Information and its transmission through the World Wide Web. You are required to
follow the Terms and Conditions while using this Website including the instructions stated
therein in respect of security and confidentiality of your Log-in and Password.
The Bank will give access to Customer Information to only authorised employees.
Employees who violate this Privacy Policy shall be subject to disciplinary process as per the
byelaws of the Bank. Any employee who withdraws from the employment of the Bank will
have to undertake to abide by this Privacy Policy and keep all Customer Information secure
and confidential.
Disclosure
    •    We shall not be held liable for disclosure of the Customer Information or Statistical
         Information in accordance with this Privacy Commitment or in terms of any other
         agreements with you.
    •    We may disclose the Statistical Information to any person, without any limitation and
         you hereby give your irrevocable consent for the same.
    •    We may disclose Customer Information to any of our associates and affiliates,
         without any limitation and you hereby give your consent for the same.
    •    We may disclose the Customer Information, to third parties, without limitation, for
         the following reasons and you hereby give your irrevocable consent for the same:-
             o To comply with legal requirements, legal process, legal or regulatory
                 directive/ instruction. or
             o To enforce the Terms and Conditions of the products or services. or
             o To protect or defend our rights, interests and property or that of our associates
                 and affiliates, or that of our or our Affiliate's employees, consultants etc. or

             o   For fraud prevention purposes. or
             o   As permitted or required by law.
      •  We may disclose the Customer Information to third parties for following, among
         other purposes, and will make reasonable efforts to bind them to obligation to keep
         the same secure and confidential and an obligation to use the information for the
         purpose for which the same is disclosed, and you hereby give your irrevocable
         consent for the same: -
             o For participation in any telecommunication or electronic clearing network. or
             o For credit rating by a credit rating agency. or
             o For advertising. or
             o For facilitating joint product promotion campaigns. or
             o For the purposes of credit reporting, verification and risk management to/ with
                 clearing house centres or credit information bureau and the like. or
             o For availing of the support services from third parties e.g. collecting
                 subscription fees, and notifying or contacting you regarding any problem with,
                 or the expiration of, any services availed by you.
 This privacy statement only covers websites that we own and control. It does not cover links from our
website to other third party websites and accordingly any information collected by the parties who own
and control those websites or their use of cookies. Please be aware that individual organizations operate
their own policies regarding the use and sale of personal information and the use of cookies. When
viewing or purchasing travel products or services from third party websites linked from our website, we
strongly recommend that you refer to the specific terms and conditions of subscription or booking, along
with the privacy policy of the third party website as these may differ from our own. These policies will
also confirm exactly who you are contracting with as part of your purchase, which is important in the
event of an incident, query or claim. If you have a concern regarding the way your personal information
will be used on other sites, then you are advised to read the relevant privacy statement or in the absence
of such a statement on the site, contact the company concerned.
